http://www.littlearmenia.com/docs/privacy.asp

Home
About
Shop
Blog
More...
Privacy Policy
LittleArmenia.com takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following
to learn more about our privacy policy.
NOTICE:
Click here
for important information about safe surfing from the Federal Trade Commission.
What this Privacy Policy Covers
This Privacy Policy covers LittleArmenia.com's treatment of personally identifiable
information that LittleArmenia.com collects when you are on the LittleArmenia.com site, and
when you use LittleArmenia.com's services.
This policy also covers LittleArmenia.com's treatment of any
personally identifiable information that LittleArmenia.com's business partners share with LittleArmenia.com
or that LittleArmenia.com may collect on a partner's site.
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that LittleArmenia.com does not own or
control, or to people that LittleArmenia.com does not employ or manage.
Information Collection and Use
LittleArmenia.com collects personally identifiable information when you use LittleArmenia.com
products or services and when you visit LittleArmenia.com pages.
LittleArmenia.com may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.
When you request certain LittleArmenia.com products or services, we may ask for your personal information,
including name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, and industry.
LittleArmenia.com also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your
browser including your IP address and the page(s) you requested.
LittleArmenia.com uses information for three general purposes:
to customize the advertising and content you see,
to fulfill your requests for certain products and services,
and to contact you about specials and new products.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
LittleArmenia.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.
LittleArmenia.com may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or
people when:
We have your consent to share the information;
We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;
We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of LittleArmenia.com to provide a
product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right
to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);
We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
We find that your actions on our web sites violate the
LittleArmenia.com Terms of Service or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or
services.
Cookies
LittleArmenia.com may set and access LittleArmenia.com cookies on your computer.
LittleArmenia.com allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of
our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer.
Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.
Advertisers or other companies do not have access to LittleArmenia.com's cookies.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
LittleArmenia.com may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes
in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent
announcement on our pages.
Questions or Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions, send them to the
webmaster@littlearmenia.com.
ages
18192021222324252627282930313233343536373839404142434445464748495051525354555657585960616263646566676869707172737475767778798081828384858687888990919293949596979899100101102103104105106107108109110111112113114115116117118119120 to 18192021222324252627282930313233343536373839404142434445464748495051525354555657585960616263646566676869707172737475767778798081828384858687888990919293949596979899100101102103104105106107108109110111112113114115116117118119120
